LE THE HOANG HAI

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

Link online portfolio

P 0868 890 658

lethehoanghai@gmail.com

B leminhquang.home.blog

G hoanghailethe

OBJECTIVE

First goal: spending next 5 years to accelerate my knowledge in every aspect of software development and sharpen my technical skills to be able to create awesome Webs/Apps that customers love to use.

Second goal: becoming a senior software engineer. Dedicate my ability and creative to a professional organization.

EXPERIENCE

2016 - 2017 Work at Atlantic Group as IR Executive

2018 - 2019 Work at Queen Land Real Estate as Sale Executive

2019 - 2020 Work at CEO Group as R&D Executive

Three key roles in previous positions:

- Research new Technology and Customers' insight.
- Design Database and analyze data to conduct reports
- Consulting for decision makers about choices, solutions

MY DEMONSTRATING PROJECT

- To-do app Written by React JS and vanilla JS
- 2. To-do app by React
- 3. Card folding game JS vanilla
- 4. Drawing Shape Site
- 5. Battle Ship game java
- 6. Tic Tac Toe game java
- 7. App Student management
- 8. Database Project (Design UML)

EDUCATION

National Economics University My major specialize in Project management, Accounting, Marketing.

PROGRAMMING LANGUAGE / **FRAME WORK**

- HTML / CSS / BOOTSTRAP
- JAVASCRIPT / JQUERRY / REACT
- **IAVA / SPRINGBOOT**
- MYSQL / DATABASE DESIGN

RELEVANT I.T KNOWLEDGE

- **GIT / GITHUB**
- **MICROSERVICE**
- **RESTFUL API**
- **CLOUD COMPUTING**
- AGILE / SCRUM
- **WORDPRESS**

NON - IT SKILLS

- ENGLISH (~ 7.0 IELTS)
- **RESEARCH**
- **CRITICAL THINKING**
- FINANCE / ACCOUNTING
- **CONTENT MARKETING**

COURSE ATTENDING

FULLSTACK DEVELOPER

CS50 HARVARD

FREECODECAMP COURSE

REACT CRASH COURSE

MYSQL DATABASE